<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About this project on The Food Items Network</title><link>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/</link><description>Recent content in About this project on The Food Items Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data collection and description</title><link>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/data-description/</guid><description>Data collection The data used in the project was collected from the BilkaToGo website using the python webscraping libraries Beautiful Soup and Selenium. The scraping was done in 2 steps. Firstly the Product Id&amp;rsquo;s, the Categories and the Price of the products was collected. Secondly the Product Id&amp;rsquo;s was used to collect the product descripstions for each item. The below figure shows what specific attributes was collected in the scraping:</description></item><item><title>Network analysis</title><link>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/network-analysis/</guid><description>In the network analysis we will delve into details giving us insights into consumer behavior in terms of how food item are purchased together. As an overview we are going to investigate the following:
The network properties to understand the overall structure that the foods-network follow by looking at the degree distribution. Investigate Assortativity to see if there is a tendency that some nodes in the network connect to other nodes that are similar in degree or based on other attributes like whether they are ecological.</description></item><item><title>Text analysis</title><link>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/text-analysis/</guid><description>We would like to get an insight in the consumer buying patterns and we could get this insight by analyzing the the words that characterize certain natural communities within the frequently-bought-together network. Here, we might get som insight in what makes products frequently bought together. In order to do this, we use the TF-IDF scores on the tokenized product descriptions. These TF-IDF scores of words help us identify what words specifically are unique for each community.</description></item></channel></rss>