<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About this project on The Food Items Network</title><link>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/</link><description>Recent content in About this project on The Food Items Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data collection and description</title><link>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/data-description/</guid><description>Data collection The data used in the project was collected from the BilkaToGo website using the python webscraping libraries Beautiful Soup and Selenium because of the site&amp;rsquo;s heavy reliance on JavaScript. The scraping was done in 2 steps.
The Product Id&amp;rsquo;s, the Categories and the Price of all products on the site was collected. The Product Id&amp;rsquo;s was used to collect the product descripstions for each item of the food-products only.</description></item><item><title>Network analysis</title><link>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/network-analysis/</guid><description>In the network analysis we will delve into details giving us insights into consumer behavior in terms of how food item are purchased together. As an overview we are going to investigate the following:
The network properties to understand the overall structure that the foods-network follow by looking at the degree distribution. Investigate Assortativity to see if there is a tendency that some nodes in the network connect to other nodes that are similar in degree and other attributes.</description></item><item><title>Text analysis</title><link>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://karolineklan.github.io/CSS_Final_Project_Group9/text-analysis/</guid><description>To gain insights into consumer buying patterns, we analyze the words that characterize certain natural communities within the frequently-bought-together network. The descriptions are a small text about each product typically explaining what the product tastes like, and what occasions/setting they are typically enjoyed in. This analysis helps us understand what underlying phrases and words characterize items that are frequently purchased together.
In order to do this, the text-analysis is made in 3 steps:</description></item></channel></rss>